Hey everyone, what's up? I got some new items from Devil Fashion I want to show you today.
Something for summer, something for clubbing. I do have a few swimsuits, although it's freezing
in here. But summer's about to come and we'll start with the first outfit. First is this PVC
top and let's just check how it looks with the jeans together. I just changed the top really
gray as you can see. Let me check the mirror. It looks cool with the shiny jeans on and the
shoes together which are also like the same look with the PVC. What I don't like
is the button row here in the pants. It's not centered so I'm going to finish the
outfit as I planned it and I'm going to add a belt. No, a skirt and a belt.
Okay, I think I want to add some gloves to the outfit.
Because I also have PVC gloves.
Let's check it out.
I think that looks really cute.
It's a really playful outfit for summer.
And you can of course wear it with or without the gloves.
I think I prefer... I think I prefer with gloves.
You could also add some arm warmers or whatever.
But let's just pretend to go to a goth beach party like that.
Maybe with other shoes.
Speaking of goth beach party, if you want to go to one, I have an even better outfit.
So let's get changed again.
it's a swimsuit and I paired it with some over knee socks so to say because I thought well the
fabric looks a bit shiny so I'm combining it with something and maybe you can tell but
I got sunburned pretty badly when I was at the Bahamas so it looks a bit ridiculous with all
the white stripes here nevertheless I'm freezing here in my studio today but I'll be in Malta in
April again so I already have something to wear there because I think this looks really cool with
all the straps in the back here and also the neck holder part I like it I do have another swimsuit
in this video which I'm going to show you later on. I changed back into some more clothes now.
This is the layer you should focus on.
It's from Double Fashion and it was a bit of a challenge to combine it to be honest
because it is completely see through so I wanted to add something on top.
it looks also kind of futuristic with all the print around so I did the mix
and match option and added a wet look bodysuit and some PVC accessories and
shoes especially the gloves they add to this really futuristic look of the
leggings and I think the combination turned out pretty cool because I can
also open the zipper. But since I do not have a matching choker I'm going to close it again.
I think some really cool straight sunglasses would work well with this look
to add to this kind of superhero matrix vibe. I don't know.
So whenever I need some funny accessories I have a look in this drawer here.
And look what I found. Futuristic glasses. Now I think that's a look. But I'm just realizing that my fake lashes are so big. I can't really even open my eyes underneath these kind of sunglasses.
so let's do it like this again and I'm going to change into the next swimsuit
surprise I promised you a swimsuit and I am wearing that swimsuit underneath this cool cloak
I paired it with some heels
some classic ones
because I think the design
is a bit more elegant
than the one
I showed you first which was a bit more
playful but
here the fabric and also with the
mesh and the buckles here
I really like
the
shoulder part here and the cut out in the back the kind of racer back also
the front I think this is the favorite of the two swimsuits of mine I kind of love that it's not
just a plain swimwear fabric here but also with a bit of pattern but I have one last outfit I want
show you you can see the hangers are already empty here and it's going to be this top
i think this is the most casual look today just the leggings and the top from devil fashion
I kind of like the crop top style the combination with the mesh and again this kind of futuristic
pattern we had in the leggings already of course I'm only showing you women's outfits but check
out devil fashion they do have a lot of men's outfit as well trousers tops a lot of cool stuff
so total recommendation if you're looking for some party outfits clubbing outfits
for summer or just to like spice up your everyday wardrobe and if you subscribe
to the newsletter you get a huge discount I think 30% but I of course
write everything down below under the video so check out the description text
I think I put makeup on the t-shirt it's always I mean there's a zipper here
which helps but still kind of a turtleneck top so putting it over the
head with a little makeup on is always in danger of getting stained somewhere
by the way this is the back side it's totally opaque and I can't really decide
which was my favorite outfit today. For the bikinis it's the second one. No the
bikini is not. It's a swimsuit. For the swimsuits it's the second one and for
the other outfits I think either the first or the second one with a skirt or
the see-through leggings. I'm not sure yet. Tell me your opinion. Leave a comment
down below and a thumbs up, subscribe to my channel and see you in the next video. Bye!